{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Drain Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/40161/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40161,"taskName":"Foundation Drainage - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Foundation Drains","xmTaskDescriptor":"Drain Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":60,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Foundation Drainage basement drains yard","textMessagingName":"Inst Found Drain","rolloverLongDesc":"Usually put in at the same time as the foundation, these drain pipes are designed to prevent wet basement problems. Though also effective as a retrofit remedy (especially in conjunction with resealing the outside of the foundation), the cost of the excavation \u0026 the disruption to landscaping make this a relatively uncommon choice for resolving wet basement problems. If uncertain about how to tackle a wet basement problem, experts recommend starting by hiring an independent consultant.","rolloverShortDesc":"Exterior drain pipes buried at base of foundation.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Foundation Drains.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Drain Installation Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Drainage Replacement","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Foundation Drainage Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Foundation Drainage - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Foundation Drainage Project","urlName":"Foundation-Drainage-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Drain Services \u0026 Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Foundation,Drainage,basement,drains,yard,,driveway,replacement","emcCategoryOid":-12033,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":471,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40161/":{"taskOID":40161,"originalTaskOID":40161,"setID":471,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5700,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this a new installation or repair of an existing foundation drainage system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Installation of new drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Installation of new drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7117,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair of existing drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Repair of existing drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7085,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Drains","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need foundation drains installed or replaced? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10762,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaks through walls","answerDisplayText":"Water leaks through walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10763,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floods during storms","answerDisplayText":"Basement floods during storms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10764,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Excessive dampness","answerDisplayText":"Excessive dampness","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10765,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete shifting or cracking","answerDisplayText":"Concrete shifting or cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10766,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discoloration, odors or rust","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration, odors or rust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10767,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold, mildew, and /or fungus","answerDisplayText":"Mold, mildew, and /or fungus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5700,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this a new installation or repair of an existing foundation drainage system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Installation of new drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Installation of new drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7117,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair of existing drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Repair of existing drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3277,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Installation of new drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Installation of new drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7117,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair of existing drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Repair of existing drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7085,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Drains","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need foundation drains installed or replaced? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10762,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaks through walls","answerDisplayText":"Water leaks through walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10763,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floods during storms","answerDisplayText":"Basement floods during storms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10764,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Excessive dampness","answerDisplayText":"Excessive dampness","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10765,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete shifting or cracking","answerDisplayText":"Concrete shifting or cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10766,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discoloration, odors or rust","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration, odors or rust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10767,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold, mildew, and /or fungus","answerDisplayText":"Mold, mildew, and /or fungus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10762,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaks through walls","answerDisplayText":"Water leaks through walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10763,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floods during storms","answerDisplayText":"Basement floods during storms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10764,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Excessive dampness","answerDisplayText":"Excessive dampness","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10765,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete shifting or cracking","answerDisplayText":"Concrete shifting or cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10766,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discoloration, odors or rust","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration, odors or rust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10767,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold, mildew, and /or fungus","answerDisplayText":"Mold, mildew, and /or fungus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}